hi folks so let's talk a little bit
大家好，让我们谈一点
about a first price auction and bidding
关于第一次价格拍卖和竞标
in a first price auction so when we look
在第一次价格拍卖中，所以当我们看
at second price auctions there's this
在第二价格拍卖中有这个
wonderful property that derives from
源自的奇妙财产
Vickrey style arguments that people have
人们有维克瑞风格的论点
a dominant strategy to be to bid their
竞标他们的主要策略
actual true valuation since they can't
实际的真实估值，因为他们无法
affect the price all they can do is
影响价格，他们所能做的就是
affect whether they're getting it good
影响他们是否过得好
or not and they want to get the good
还是不，他们想得到好的
when their values above the next highest
当它们的值高于下一个最高值时
bid in first price auctions you're
参与您的首次价格拍卖
actually paying what you bid and so if
实际支付您的出价，如果
you tell people your valuation as your
你告诉别人你的估值是你的
bid and you win you're going to end up
出价，您赢了，您将要结束
with with no surplus because you're
没有盈余，因为你
paying exactly what you think the items
完全按照您的想法付款
worth you get nothing out of it so here
值得你一无所获，所以在这里
you're going to have an incentive to
你将有动力去
shade your bid and that means that the
遮盖您的出价，这意味着
bidding and first price auctions we're
拍卖和第一价格拍卖
going to solve as an equilibrium as a
将作为一个平衡来解决
base in equilibrium we're not going to
在均衡基础上，我们不会
have dominant strategies and things
有主导策略和事物
you're going to be more complicated so
你会变得更复杂
let's start by just comparing the first
让我们从比较第一个开始
price option to another class of
另一类的价格选择
auctions the Dutch auctions and just
拍卖荷兰拍卖会，
noting that these things are
注意到这些东西是
strategically equivalent and what does
战略上等价的，做什么
that mean in terms of strategically
在战略上意味着
equivalent it means that as a function
等价意味着它是一个功能
of the valuations of the individuals the
个人的估值
outcomes are going to be the same in
结果将是相同的
terms of the eventual payments and
最终付款条款和
allocations of the objects and in
对象和对象的分配
particular there's a mapping between the
特别是在
strategies in these two games that say
这两个游戏中的策略说
that for an equilibrium in one of them
为了其中之一的平衡
we find an equivalent equilibrium and
我们找到一个等效的平衡
the other one and in particular just to
另一个，尤其是
understand what's going on here
了解这里发生了什么
in both of these auctions you've got to
在这两次拍卖中，您必须
make a decision on how much you're
决定你要多少钱
willing to bid conditional on it being
愿意以此为条件出价
the highest bid and not knowing anything
最高出价，一无所知
else about the other individuals values
关于其他个人的价值观
so Dutch auctions are an extensive form
因此荷兰式拍卖是广泛的形式
so basically what's happening is that
所以基本上发生的是
the price starts at a very high level it
价格从很高的水平开始
starts dropping down and then we keep
开始下降，然后我们继续
going until somebody grabs it okay now
直到有人抓住它好了
once you grab it what do you know all
一旦你抓住它，你知道什么
you know is you grabbed it at some price
你知道你以一定的价格抢了吗
and everyone else is still below you so
而且其他人仍然在你下方
beforehand I could just start a state a
事先我可以开始一个状态
price and
价格和
okay look if nobody's grabbed it so far
好吧，看看到目前为止，没有人抓住它
at this price this is what I'm going to
以这个价格，这就是我要去的
be willing to bid so conditional on me
愿意出价以我为条件
being the highest this is what I'm
我是最高的
willing to put in and so that strategy
愿意投入等等策略
of figuring out where you want the clock
弄清楚你想要时钟的地方
to go down to before you grab it is
在你抓住它之前下降到
equivalent to just writing down your
相当于只写下您的
value in a piece of paper and saying
在一张纸上说的价值
okay the highest person wins because I
好吧，最高的人赢了，因为我
have to make a decision on how much I'm
必须决定我多少钱
willing to pay conditional on that being
愿意为此付出条件
more than what everybody else wrote on
比其他人写的更多
their slips of paper okay so the we end
他们的纸条好吧，所以我们结束了
up with the the same strategic analysis
进行相同的战略分析
basically why do we see both of these
基本上为什么我们看到这两个
different kinds of auctions still use
各种拍卖仍在使用
and practice then so one nice thing
然后练习，那么一件好事
about first price auction sealed bid
关于第一次价格拍卖的密封投标
auctions is you can have people bid at
拍卖是可以让人们竞标的
asynchronously so a lot of procurement
异步的，所以很多采购
auctions might be that done this way so
拍卖可能是这样完成的
for instance the government might say
例如政府可能会说
what you know you know you bid on a
你所知道的，你知道你对一个出价
certain contract put your bid in an
某些合同将您的出价
envelope and send it to us actually
信封并实际发送给我们
procurement auctions if you're trying to
采购拍卖，如果您尝试
sell something government usually is the
卖东西通常是政府
lower bid lowest bid that wins but those
较低的出价获胜的最低出价，但那些
can be held to asynchronously everybody
可以异步地所有人
can just mail their things in then you
可以邮寄他们的东西，然后你
open up the things and whichever is the
打开东西，无论是
winning bid is then picked out of the
然后从中标出中标
envelopes
信封
I'm dr. auctions in contrast you could
我是博士相比之下，您可以进行拍卖
have to have the people together and
必须让人们在一起
sitting there watching the clock go down
坐在那里看着时钟下来
but the nice thing about those auctions
但是那些拍卖的好处
is you don't need as much communication
你不需要太多的交流吗
in the sense that all you need to do is
从某种意义上说，您需要做的就是
have this thing drop and then somebody
让这东西掉下来然后有人
to say yes at some point so only one bit
在某个时候说是，所以只有一点点
needs to be transmitted from the bidders
需要从投标人那里转达
to the auctioneer so it's very efficient
给拍卖师，所以非常有效率
in terms of information communication
在信息交流方面
you have the clock dropping down and
你的时钟下降了
then somebody saying give it to me so so
然后有人说给我
you know there are different auctions in
你知道有不同的拍卖
terms of the actual implementation okay
实际执行的条件还可以
how should people bid on these auctions
人们应该如何竞标这些拍卖
well as we mentioned just a few minutes
就像我们提到的几分钟
ago bid less than your valuation because
之前的出价低于您的估值，因为
it in basically deciding how load a bid
基本上是决定如何加载出价
is going to be the tricky part because
将成为棘手的部分，因为
you've got a trade off the lower the you
您的交易越低，您的交易就越便宜
make your bid the lower the amount you
降低您的出价
pay but also the lower the probability
支付，但概率也较低
that you win so you're trading off
你赢了，所以你在权衡
probability of winning against amount
赢得金额的可能性
that you are having to pay
你必须付钱
and so now you don't have a dominant
所以现在你没有统治力
strategy how low you want to go actually
策略您实际想走多低
depends on what other people are doing
取决于其他人在做什么
so if I think other people going to bid
所以如果我认为其他人会出价
very very low then I'm going to be
非常非常低，那么我将成为
willing to lower my bed a lot if I think
如果我想，我愿意把床降低很多
other people are going to be bidding
其他人将要出价
fairly aggressively I might have to keep
我可能会非常积极地保持
my bit higher so I can't make my
我高一点，所以我做不到
decision of how I should bid without
决定我应该如何竞标
knowing exactly what the bids of others
确切知道别人的出价
are and so now we don't have a dominant
是的，所以现在我们没有主导地位
strategy I don't have one thing which is
策略我没有一件事是
best to do irregardless of what other
最好不管其他事情
people are doing I have to think about
人们在做我必须考虑的事情
what they're doing and calculating my
他们在做什么并计算我的
bid okay so let's have a quick look at
好吧，让我们快速看一下
an equilibrium of one of these and see
其中之一的平衡，看
how how we can least verify something in
我们如何最少能验证某些东西
the equilibrium and then we'll talk a
平衡，然后我们将讨论
little bit about how you might find
关于您可能如何找到的一点
equilibria in these auctions which is
在这些拍卖中的均衡是
not going to be always extremely easy so
不会总是那么容易，所以
let's think of a first price auction so
让我们考虑一下第一次价格拍卖
let's start with a very simple case to
让我们从一个非常简单的案例开始
analyze first two bidders both
分析前两个竞标者
risk-neutral and they get an independent
风险中立，他们获得了独立
draw from a uniform distribution on zero
从零上的均匀分布得出
one okay so each of these two bidders so
一个可以，所以这两个竞标者都这样
we've got two bidders each person
我们每个人都有两个竞标者
uniform zero one valuations and those
统一零一估值和那些
are drawn independently and the claim
独立绘制，索赔
here is that if we look at we want to
这是如果我们看一下我们想
get a Bayesian Nash equilibrium of this
得到这个的贝叶斯纳什均衡
game what are we going to have the bids
游戏我们要如何出价
are just going to be each person drops
只是每个人都会掉下来
their value by half so if my values are
他们的价值减半，所以如果我的价值是
3/4 I'll save 3/8 if my value is 1/2
3/4如果我的值是1/2，我会节省3/8
I'll say 1/4 right so I just take
我会说1/4对，所以我就拿
whatever my value is and I just shade it
不管我的价值是多少
by 1/2 and that's my bid ok and so let's
加1/2，那是我的出价，所以让我们
go through and just verify that that's
经过并只是验证那是
amazing Nash equilibrium okay so we want
纳什均衡惊人，所以我们想要
to check whether this is in equilibrium
检查这是否处于平衡状态
so let's given the symmetry here we can
所以让我们在这里给出对称性
just check for one of the bidders so
只是检查投标人之一，所以
let's suppose that the other bidder is
假设另一个竞标者是
actually whatever their value is they
实际上，不管他们的价值是什么
bid a half of it and now we think about
出价一半，现在我们考虑
bitter one and let's let bitter one
苦一，让我们苦一
choose a strategy s1 of how high they're
选择他们有多高的策略s1
going to bid as a function of their
将根据他们的出价
value okay so if I'm bidding s1 so let's
值还行，所以如果我要竞标s1，就让我们
suppose I put a bit of s1 in and the
假设我把s1放进去
other bidder is bidding half of their
其他竞标者正在竞标一半
value so what am I going to win I'm
值，所以我要赢得什么
going to win one 1/2 of the
要赢得1/2的
two is less than s 1 or V 2 is less than
2小于s 1或V 2小于
2 s 1 ok and what's my payoff then my
2 s 1好，那我的收益是多少
payoff is V 1 minus s 1 but I'm going to
收益是V 1减去s 1，但我要
lose whenever the the other individual
每当其他人失去
bid when V 2 over 2 is bigger than s 1
V 2 over 2大于s 1时的出价
or V 2 is bigger than 2 s 1 and then I
或V 2大于2 s 1然后我
get a utility of 0 ok so in terms of
得到0的效用，所以在
figuring out what my value is there's
弄清楚我的价值是
cases where I win the auction so I can
我赢得拍卖的情况下，我可以
integrate over those where V 2 is up to
在V 2达到
2 over s 1 and then I'm getting this and
2比s 1，然后我得到这个
otherwise if the value of the other
否则，如果对方的价值
person is bigger than 2 s 1 I'm going to
人大于2 s 1我要
get 0 so this is my expected utility
得到0，所以这是我期望的效用
it's simple integral integrate that
简单的积分整合
thing what do you get you get 2 V 1
你得到什么，你得到2 V 1
times s 1 minus 2 s 1 squared okay very
时间s 1减去2 s 1平方好
simple expression so we have an expected
简单的表达，所以我们有一个期望
utility as a function of what my s 1 is
效用是我的s 1的函数
conditional any other person following
有条件的任何其他人关注
this prescribed strategy so let's
这个规定的策略，所以让我们
differentiate that with respect to s 1
关于s 1进行区分
set it equal to 0 so when we do that
将其设置为0，所以当我们这样做时
what do we end up with we end up with s
我们最终得到什么，我们最终得到s
1 equals 1/2 V 1 as being the solution
1等于1/2 V 1作为解决方案
to setting that equal to 0 so if you
设置为等于0，所以如果你
want to maximize this and you can check
想要最大化这个，你可以检查
the second-order conditions you want to
您想要的二阶条件
maximize this indeed here we end up with
最大化这确实是我们最终的结果
a condition where my optimal bid given
我的最佳出价给出的条件
it the other person is bidding half
对方出价一半
their value is 2 bid half my value as
他们的价值是我的价值的2一半
well ok so and again the calculation for
好吧，一次又一次的计算
the other person is exactly symmetric to
另一个人与
this so this is the basic Nash
这就是基本的纳什
equilibrium of this game so what we've
这个游戏的平衡，所以我们已经
got is people bidding down and they're
有人叫低价，他们是
trading off a calculation implicitly in
隐式权衡计算
terms of what we're doing here if we
我们在这里做什么的条件
want to look at the calculation that we
想看一下我们的计算
were doing by increasing your by
通过增加你的
decreasing your bid the the gain is that
降低您的出价，收益是
you pay less conditional on winning but
您支付获胜的条件较少，但
you also win less of the time so the
您也赢得较少的时间，所以
trade off is coming at your you're
权衡即将到来
winning less of the time but then you're
赢得更少的时间，然后你就
paying less when you do win and so that
赢钱时少付钱，这样
trade-off is exactly
权衡是恰到好处
captured to this maximization problem
抓住了这个最大化问题
and you want to shade your bid by a half
而您想将出价降低一半
okay um this is obviously a very narrow
好吧，这显然是非常狭窄的
result we did two bidders uniform
结果我们做了两个投标人制服
valuations so we need to solve for this
估值，所以我们需要解决这个问题
thing because this is not incentive
事情，因为这不是激励
compatible as a direct mechanism in
作为直接机制兼容
terms of dominant strategies right so
占主导地位的策略对吧
it's not a dominant we have no dominant
它不是统治者，我们没有统治者
strategies here we're not getting
的策略，我们没有得到
dominant strategy instead of
主导策略而不是
compatibility when you dissolve four the
溶解性时的四个
equilibrium and no more generally you
平衡，而不是一般而言
could solve for you know if we had n
可以解决您的问题，如果我们知道
bidders instead of two what would
竞标者而不是两个
devalue what would the equilibrium look
贬值均衡的面貌
like then it's going to look like
就像那样
instead of shading your bid by a half
而不是将出价降低一半
you should general formula is going to
你应该将通用公式
be n minus 1 over n right so when n is 2
是n减去n的1，所以当n是2时
this is 1/2 when n is 3 then it's going
这是1/2当n为3时
to be 2/3 when n is 4 you go up to 3/4
当n为4时为2/3，则上升到3/4
and so forth and so you just keep
依此类推，所以你只要保持
climbing in terms of how much you're
根据你的身高攀升
bidding and what's happening well it
竞标及其进展顺利
gets harder and harder to win with more
越来越难赢得更多
and more people in the auction you're
还有更多人在拍卖中
going to have to bid closer and closer
将不得不越来越接近
to your value to have a chance to win
以您的价值来赢得机会
and then the trade-off is just that you
然后权衡就是你
know as you as you lower your bid much
当您降低出价时就知道
beyond something that's a very close to
超越了非常接近的东西
your bid you have no chance of winning
您的出价，您将没有中奖的机会
and so you're going to end up having
因此，您最终将不得不拥有
this trade-off be closer to the actual
这种权衡更接近实际
value you can go through and do the
您可以经历并做的价值
calculation it's going to be very
计算这将是非常
similar to what we did just a different
类似于我们所做的不同
calculation in terms of integrals now
现在按照积分计算
you're going to win when everybody's
当每个人都
below you not just the other person
在你下面，而不仅仅是另一个人
below you so that's a slightly more
在你下面，所以稍微多一点
complicated integration but basically
复杂的整合，但基本上
exactly the same logic we just did for
我们刚才做的逻辑完全相同
the two bitter case okay so broader
这两个痛苦的情况还好，范围更广
problem what we did here is we only
问题，我们在这里所做的只是
verified that this was in equilibrium so
验证这是平衡的，所以
we guessed the equilibrium and then
我们猜到了平衡，然后
verified it I'm how do you actually find
验证它，我实际上是如何找到的
an equilibrium in these cases well if
在这些情况下，如果
it's not a nice uniform distribution and
这不是一个很好的均匀分布，
guessing that it's going to be a linear
猜测它将是线性的
function of your value then you've got
您的价值的功能，那么你已经
to guess more complicated functions and
猜测更复杂的功能
there's going to be basically some
基本上会有一些
integration problems which will give you
整合问题会给你
some ideas of how this works for certain
关于某些方法的一些想法
distributions for arbitrary
任意分布
distributions the bidding function can
分配竞标功能可以
be much more complicated functions and
功能要复杂得多
basically it will
基本上它将
we be described up to some integration
我们将描述一些集成
conditions so there are papers that give
条件，所以有论文可以
some solutions to this there's a paper
一些解决方案，有一篇论文
by Milton Weber in 1982 there's some
Milton Weber在1982年写的
other papers out there which will give
那里的其他论文会给
some background on on solving these
解决这些问题的一些背景
kinds of auctions that that first price
第一种价格的拍卖
auction actually has been solved in
拍卖实际上已经在
quite early on in the literature but
在文献中还很早，但是
more generally solving these ones when
更普遍地解决这些问题时
we don't have gone on strategies is
我们没有继续执行策略
going to involve some guesses and in
将涉及一些猜测和
some cases there might be some
有些情况下可能会有一些
integration conditions that will give us
整合条件将给我们
nice solutions but they often won't
好的解决方案，但它们通常不会
exist in closed form and especially here
以封闭形式存在，尤其是在这里
also the symmetry helps a lot so if you
对称性也有很大帮助，所以如果您
have asymmetric auctions things can be
进行非对称拍卖
difficult and more generally even
困难，甚至更普遍
finding weather equilibria exists in
发现存在天气平衡
these worlds is not an easy problem
这些世界不是一个容易的问题
there's a literature they in fact I've
他们实际上有一种文学
worked on a bit about existence of
对存在的存在进行了一些研究
equilibria and auctions so one thing
平衡和拍卖是一回事
about equilibria and auctions is they're
关于均衡和拍卖是他们
discontinuous I changed my bid a little
不连续，我稍微更改了出价
and I might be going from winning the
我可能会从赢得
object to not winning the object and so
反对不赢得目标等等
suddenly my payoff goes from being
突然我的收获就消失了
positive to being zero and that this
积极为零，这
continuity means that I might not always
连续性意味着我可能并不总是
have nicely defined best responses that
有明确定义的最佳回应，
are going to move in ways that were used
将以过去的方式移动
that the implicit proofs of existence
存在的隐含证据
before made nice use of the best
善用最好的之前
response correspondence that that it's
是的对应
not going to have the properties that
不会有那些
used to have any discontinuous games and
曾经玩过任何不连续的游戏，
getting equilibrium and existence in
获得平衡和存在
these kinds of auction settings this is
这些拍卖设置是
quite tricky and there's some things
很棘手，有些事情
that are known about settings where
关于设置的已知信息
there do exist equilibria there also
那里确实存在均衡
some examples where they don't exist
一些不存在的例子
equilibria so that's actually an
平衡，所以实际上
interesting project on its own so
有趣的项目本身
different kinds of auctions different
不同种类的拍卖不同
kinds of equilibria they're related to
与它们相关的各种均衡
each other and we'll see more about that
彼此，我们将看到更多有关此的信息
in a bit
有点